<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="C601FADB-88C9-4541-8C4D-BFF050C9E948">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20210124" date="2021-01-24 14:16:54 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Boulder Modem Ski Day</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Friday, April 1, 2011</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Planning for the Modem Ski Day on Friday, showing off Phresheez to folks (to track each other)...and on wednesday, my Droid goes nuts.  The touch screen takes phantom presses all over the place.  The second time it happened, it decided to call Troy (whilst he was on vacation with the familiy at Disney World).  Tried to power it off...but that button just turns off the screen when a call is in progress.  Finally pulled the battery...he calls back because he thinks it&#x2019;s an emergency.  &#x201C;No, just a butt-dial.&#x201D;  Look around, and the Thunderbolt is out...our 9k with 7x30.  I know of the issues we have, and know it&#x2019;s gonna suck as far as battery life, but I decide to get it anyways.  Long story short (too late!)  I&#x2019;m without tracking for a while.&#xD;&#xD;The Boulder Modem Ski day was on my bday...nice day to ditch work.  Had QC pay for lift tix and lessons for those who wanted &#x2018;em.  Did some warmup runs under Pano with Chuck, Ehren, Kurt, Matt, Stan, Tom, and Praveen...then took Matt, Kurt and Ehren on some bump runs.  When Matt and Kurt&#x2019;s legs didn&#x2019;t have any more juice, I took Ehren on Runaway and Topher&#x2019;s Trees.  Met up with the crew under Olympia.  &#xD;&#xD;Did dinner at Beau Jos....then headed back over the pass to Fraser and the rest of my weekend.  Come in, start unloading, and Max says he wants to show me something.  Claps his hands, and Gunter comes out from behind the couch!!!  WAAAAYYY surprised!  Great Bday!</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
