<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="A1219B8D-2973-46FD-8BB1-40BCF8C95E47">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20210123" date="2021-01-24 01:15:50 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Pano Open&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, January 28, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sitting at the bump jam apres wednesday, and I get a page from Alli:  &#x201C;If pano was opening tomorrow, would you want to know?&#x201D;  Gunter made some turns up there on thursday, and we got a decent dump on friday (with the top closed!).  So, Saturday rolls around, I drop off Max, and head straight there.  Good timing...there was a queue, and they JUST were opening the lift.  I made about the 30th chair.&#xD;&#xD;The top was windy and windblown, but the trees were good.  Did laps through Johnson&#x2019;s, Willet&#x2019;s, and Kinnikinic, then decided to see if the upper switchyard trees were open.  They were, and it was glorious!  But, after hearing about the accident last weekend, after one lap, I decided I shouldn&#x2019;t be doing those alone, and headed to pioneer.  &#xD;&#xD;Gunter then gives me a page, and I head back over.  We did lap after lap over there...good stuff!!  Really reminds me how much I love the powdery trees!!!&#xD;&#xD;Other (newly) open terrain:  Pine Cliffs (yay!), Super Gauge Trail (enabling the Franken).  Pine Cliffs was hard-packed, but nice to be able to ski something with some pitch to it.  Still closed:  Runaway and the Chutes, Brian&#x2019;s, Stagecoach &amp; Sundance, Larkspur, Sky Pilot, Fireberry, and all of Eagle Wind.   &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="28_Entry_1_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="478px" height="358px"/>
</content>
