<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="FDDC2949-73CB-4522-8920-DDA5BFA3F56E">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20210123" date="2021-01-24 01:17:00 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Yard Sale on the Chutes&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, February 9, 2014&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Snow for the weekend:  a few inches each day from wednesday through sunday.  Alli rented some Super7s to see what this downhill fat ski thing was all about.  Max was supposed to have a comp on Saturday, but because of wind, they ended up closing Eskimo (along with Hi-Lo, Pano, Pioneer, and Eagle)....so the comp got cancelled.  Took her through the do-or-die trees and upper Tohpers...she&#x2019;s hooked.   :)  They ended up going back early on Saturday, so I was on my own for Sunday.&#xD;&#xD;Drove down early to Jane, and there&#x2019;s a line of cars waiting at the pass.  Woo hoo!  Pass closed; small crowds!!!  I end up getting 11th chair up the Gauge, and have some fun first runs (although the snow wasn&#x2019;t all that deep...still, can&#x2019;t complain).  They opened up the back stagecoach gate, even though eagle wasn&#x2019;t open...decent stashes back there.  I then had an epic run through the frenchy trees, and nailed the frenchman bumps.  Chutes were open, so I headed over there.&#xD;&#xD;Decide to start with No-Name.  Couple turns in, and I backseat, and kaboom....yard sale.  I start sliding...slowly.  Get my feet pointed down, still can&#x2019;t stop.  Slide pretty much to the bottom...you can see from the Google Earth image above how far.  Wait for a little bit, but since the crowds are low, no one else is coming down.  Fine.  I start the hike back up to my skis and poles...about 300&#x2019; later, I&#x2019;m there.  Needless to say, I&#x2019;m *still* a little shaken.&#xD;&#xD;Checked out the elevation change; looks to be only about 200&#x2019;, which would put this at 30 degrees.  Sure feels like closer to 45.  &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;ve got the hike marked as the yellow line above...the GPS didn&#x2019;t do so hot tracking it (probably because I was hugging the hill going up).  Google&#x2019;s elevation profile is below...&#xD;&#xD;Here&#x2019;s an older chute pic, with the hike marked with the black line...&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="9_Yard_Sale_on_the_Chutes_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="700px" height="400px"/>
</content>
