<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="A1219B8D-2973-46FD-8BB1-40BCF8C95E47">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20210123" date="2021-01-24 01:15:50 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Bump Jam&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, January 25, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Took off from work to do the first bump jam of the season with Gunter.  We expected it to be lightly attended...but there were about 45 folks there.   There were 4 hard-core skiers (including gunter), and a whole bunch more of the &#x201C;blue-black&#x201D; folks.  We had a group of ~10 that were more on the aggressive side, including a bunch of elder, high-maintenance folks that were part of the &#x201C;old farts&#x201D; club.  We did our eval on narrow gauge instead of spike (as the pony wasn&#x2019;t running)...everyone was at about the same level.  Bob himself ended up taking the older gents (whew!) and I wound up with Nigel.  Tom and Gernot were both teaching as well, and found out that Merrick went to Vail.  The funny thing:  Nigel is &#x201C;party pam&#x2019;s&#x201D; husband.  Kinda cool.&#xD;&#xD;Spent most of our time over on the park side, as there were fewer rocks.  The big take-aways for me this time:  my knees are bending and absorbing now (yay!), but my upper body is too far back.  He&#x2019;s getting me to bend forward at the waist...this really feels like I&#x2019;m hunching.  I&#x2019;m gonna wanna do video this weekend to see it...I&#x2019;m betting that it actually looks more balanced.  The other one was to really REACH downhill with my pole.  So from Gernot&#x2019;s lesson, I&#x2019;m finally planting, but now I need to EXTEND.  I can do this fairly well with my right hand, but my left wants to stay tucked (or chicken-winged).  I&#x2019;m guessing that&#x2019;s from years of drumming...thats the natural position for hitting the snare.  :)&#xD;&#xD;One fun moment:  heading back to the jane side, getting off the Olympia.  They start heading for Jane, and I pull up:  &#x201C;Guys, Frenchman is over *there* (pointing)&#x201D;  Multiple looks of exasperation, but one lady says &#x201C;okay, fine go do it&#x201D;.  &#x201C;I&#x2019;ll do it if you do it...&#x201D;  And the group ends up going down frenchman.  One of the guys in our class tells the story about how his first day on skis he went down frenchman and has been terrified of it ever since...and going down it today fixed that.  &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="25_Bump_Jam_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="298px" height="300px"/>
</content>
