<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>2011/2012 Recaps</title>
    <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/2011_2012.html</link>
    <description>The final season counts:&lt;br/&gt;Glenn: 57&lt;br/&gt;Max: 40&lt;br/&gt;Günter:  31&lt;br/&gt;Alli: 30</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/2011_2012_files/1_29_cirque_from_belle.jpg</url>
      <title>2011/2012 Recaps</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/2011_2012.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/4/21_Metrics.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c944032d-aab5-444a-97f7-3049b0894353</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 18:43:28 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>With the snowpack melting quickly, and temps in the 70s up at Fraser, I’m giving up on the season.  Okay, I really gave up after spring break.  Here are the various breakdowns.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I’m not gonna do the “days between folks” thing here...you should have seen that from the previous page.   First up:  year-over-year comparisons:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Closing Day</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/4/15_Jane_Closing_Day.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">337ae17f-297d-4a96-a479-4ef6bef13e67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 06:32:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/4/15_Jane_Closing_Day_files/droppedImage_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object209_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:217px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Jane had an end-of-season treat...6” of fresh snow for closing day.  I had the summer storage wax on the S7s, so I scraped it off, and headed out.  Funny, this is the way the resort was *supposed* to look all year long.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We went down for the party in the C-Lot...Alli dressed up as Jane, and Max made a robot costume.  Alli and Max wanted to hang out in the lot, so I ran up and got early tracks. Headed straight for Pano, but they had Animal Control up there to take care of some Moose!  (That lift never did open).  Did a bunch of trees instead...was the first one through the backside switchyard trees.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/4/15_Jane_Closing_Day_files/droppedImage_1.jpg" length="20338" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mayor and Mary Jane</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/29_Entry_1.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62a3a0a6-fd0a-4432-a52e-ee9ca8c7f847</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 08:35:36 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/29_Entry_1_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object210_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:123px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Alli and the Mayor decided to dress up, ski around, and say “Hi” at the Alpine nationals.  Played around some, generally was silly.  </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/29_Entry_1_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="89404" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/27_Spring_Break.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b658879-2c09-41c3-b6a8-8a65b2ac9fe5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 08:56:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/27_Spring_Break_files/droppedImage_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object211_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:217px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Everything is melting quickly, and we’re in that spring condition time where the mornings are icy and the afternoons are slushy.  Even the CH10 sticks when the outside temp gets above 50....but it’s good core muscle work.  :)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Saturday Max had Freestyle tryouts with Jenn...he did really well.  She said he’s *defintly* ready for the freestyle program, if he’s ready to push himself.  He wasn’t so sure, but she told him she thinks he should.  I think he likes her as a coach.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday was playing around...took some vids.  Will merge ‘em into a master video for the week later.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Monday was *supposed* to be a day of rest for me, but I experimented with sandpaper and structure.  Note:  I’m *never* doing that again.  Only did one ski, and it was really tough getting the ptex hairs back under control.  Went out to do a couple “experiment” runs, and I couldn’t tell a difference.  The good news is that I didn’t make that ski worse!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gunter’s been sick, and Max and Mom wanted an adventure day, so I went out solo today.  NO ONE was at the resort...showed up at about 10, and got prime parking at the MJ base.  Cruising the groomers was the way to go...made my way over to pioneer.  Sundance is closed due to grass, but you can do lift line, and then they had buckaroo, Quickdraw, and Shootout open.  Did some speed runs there.  Also had some fun in the Jabberwocky bumps...hit ‘em as quick as I could.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Closures:  the top cruisers at Vasquez, bumpy part of columbine, trestle and the rest of challenger around to boiler, and Outhouse.  The bottom is pretty slushy...I *really* don’t think they’re gonna make it to mid april.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/27_Spring_Break_files/droppedImage_1.jpg" length="24252" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freestyle Competition</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/11_Freestyle_Competition.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05732aba-b63a-4000-8cef-2eaed843be91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 07:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/11_Freestyle_Competition_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object212_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:123px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gunter came out again for the weekend...snow at WP is also starting to get sketchy.  We need more snow badly, and nothing significant is in the forecast.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sunday was another freestyle comp...Max wanted to do the Parkway course again.  This time they had it set up to be bumps to a decent jump.  Film below...Max placed 8th.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/11_Freestyle_Competition_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="55723" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QC Ski Day</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/9_QC_Ski_Day.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">523476eb-107d-4703-baa5-d6e0800cd4b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Mar 2012 07:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/9_QC_Ski_Day_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object213_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:180px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;This year’s destination - Breckenridge.  Take the bus up, get ready to gear up, and I notice I’ve got Alli’s boots.  Bummer!  Go do the rental thing, and after about an hour, I’m ready to hit the slopes.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Breck’s ratings are...shall we say...inflated.  What they are classifying as a black could easily be a blue at WP or Alta.  Did a couple laps off of Peak 10 (Falcon Chair).  To the far left were some double-black bump runs..decided to give them a try.  The coverage over there was *really* bad though...stuff sticking through on *EVERY* mogul.  Finally picked my way down, and started doing the right side (towards peak 9).  Met up with RichardS, RichardR, AJ, CurtM, Matthias, Bijan, and eventually TC there...did some bump runs here, then went over to the imperial chair and the hike.  *Much* tougher hike than Catherine’s or the Cirque...you end up at about 13k.  Caught my breath, and we worked our way over to the lake chutes. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;They classify these as double-black “expert” (as opposed to the standard double black), and yeah, it’s tough.  Pretty steep drop in...got some shots of the crew.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bus ride back was standard....which is a good thing.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/9_QC_Ski_Day_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="68949" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March Begins</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/4_March_Begins.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eac4505e-7e41-47d1-91a5-fa9a7b7fddad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 4 Mar 2012 19:35:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/4_March_Begins_files/IMAG0127.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object214_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:240px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;So last weekend, Alli had a bunch of Rugby folks up.  The conditions were pretty evil though.  Did a couple laps through Eagle Wind; pretty windblown.  Went down to Pioneer, met up with Max’s class, just in time for the lift to be shut down due to wind.  We hiked up, and got a snowmobile tow out.  Dave &amp;amp; the rest of the ATP Devo crew kept going, even though only Arrow and Gemini were open...and eventually they opened Eskimo back up.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This weekend, Max was sick saturday morning, so I went out solo.  COLD day...mostly due to wind chill.  Still made it from lifts open straight through to a little before 3.  The annoying news:  Phresheez didn’t track me last sunday, nor on the 3rd.  Took a peek at it, and it says it’s having trouble storing the data. I’ll ping the guys over there and see what they say.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Today was a Max day...much better weather.  We did a bunch of laps through Eagle Wind (found the Mayor’s office!), Pioneer, and Jane-side bumps.  Oh, and in case you didn’t notice from the picture above, Runaway (and the Chutes!) were open.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/3/4_March_Begins_files/IMAG0127.jpg" length="142075" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alta   </title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/20_Alta.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c061031-9331-4aa7-bdcc-ca032561ac73</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 06:07:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/20_Alta_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object215_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:123px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;President’s Day Weekend...for the second year in a row, we decide to hit Alta rather than the crowds at WP.  Stayed up at the Goldminer’s Daughter, a lodge at the Wildcat base, right at the Wildcat and Collins lifts.  Pretty cool...they did breakfast and dinner, and had a nifty “wrecking room” (rec room?) that Max dug, with Ping Pong and Pool.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Not as much snow as last year, but still skied the full 3 days.  Here’s the vid:</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/20_Alta_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="244607" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy’s Weekend</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/12_Boys_Weekend.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b7ea1b3-2960-45bf-a824-c1990a068377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 07:30:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/12_Boys_Weekend_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object216_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:123px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Alli had rugby in vegas this weekend...Gunter came out, and we carried on the “boy’s weekend” tradition.  He got some Icelandic Keepers...took ‘em in on Saturday to get ‘em mounted, and picked them up on Sunday.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Saturday was spent making laps in the upper switchyard trees.  They had 4” for each of the past 3 days, so there was definitely decent snow in there.  Here’s the vid from Saturday:</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/2/12_Boys_Weekend_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="115871" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pano Open</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/28_Entry_1.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8d0d4aa-9603-4b7c-9f43-19602bf711f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 06:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/28_Entry_1_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object217_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:218px; height:163px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Sitting at the bump jam apres wednesday, and I get a page from Alli:  “If pano was opening tomorrow, would you want to know?”  Gunter made some turns up there on thursday, and we got a decent dump on friday (with the top closed!).  So, Saturday rolls around, I drop off Max, and head straight there.  Good timing...there was a queue, and they JUST were opening the lift.  I made about the 30th chair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The top was windy and windblown, but the trees were good.  Did laps through Johnson’s, Willet’s, and Kinnikinic, then decided to see if the upper switchyard trees were open.  They were, and it was glorious!  But, after hearing about the accident last weekend, after one lap, I decided I shouldn’t be doing those alone, and headed to pioneer.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gunter then gives me a page, and I head back over.  We did lap after lap over there...good stuff!!  Really reminds me how much I love the powdery trees!!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Other (newly) open terrain:  Pine Cliffs (yay!), Super Gauge Trail (enabling the Franken).  Pine Cliffs was hard-packed, but nice to be able to ski something with some pitch to it.  Still closed:  Runaway and the Chutes, Brian’s, Stagecoach &amp;amp; Sundance, Larkspur, Sky Pilot, Fireberry, and all of Eagle Wind.   </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/28_Entry_1_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="66278" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bump Jam</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/25_Bump_Jam.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aff0405a-09bf-40ad-a790-ef57a35c5256</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 05:35:39 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/25_Bump_Jam_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object218_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:225px; height:227px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Took off from work to do the first bump jam of the season with Gunter.  We expected it to be lightly attended...but there were about 45 folks there.   There were 4 hard-core skiers (including gunter), and a whole bunch more of the “blue-black” folks.  We had a group of ~10 that were more on the aggressive side, including a bunch of elder, high-maintenance folks that were part of the “old farts” club.  We did our eval on narrow gauge instead of spike (as the pony wasn’t running)...everyone was at about the same level.  Bob himself ended up taking the older gents (whew!) and I wound up with Nigel.  Tom and Gernot were both teaching as well, and found out that Merrick went to Vail.  The funny thing:  Nigel is “party pam’s” husband.  Kinda cool.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Spent most of our time over on the park side, as there were fewer rocks.  The big take-aways for me this time:  my knees are bending and absorbing now (yay!), but my upper body is too far back.  He’s getting me to bend forward at the waist...this really feels like I’m hunching.  I’m gonna wanna do video this weekend to see it...I’m betting that it actually looks more balanced.  The other one was to really REACH downhill with my pole.  So from Gernot’s lesson, I’m finally planting, but now I need to EXTEND.  I can do this fairly well with my right hand, but my left wants to stay tucked (or chicken-winged).  I’m guessing that’s from years of drumming...thats the natural position for hitting the snare.  :)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One fun moment:  heading back to the jane side, getting off the Olympia.  They start heading for Jane, and I pull up:  “Guys, Frenchman is over *there* (pointing)”  Multiple looks of exasperation, but one lady says “okay, fine go do it”.  “I’ll do it if you do it...”  And the group ends up going down frenchman.  One of the guys in our class tells the story about how his first day on skis he went down frenchman and has been terrified of it ever since...and going down it today fixed that.  </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/25_Bump_Jam_files/showmap.jpg" length="18098" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunter Weekend #1</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/22_Weekend_With_Gunter.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d402207-fa41-4543-982f-9f11893af263</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 06:45:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/22_Weekend_With_Gunter_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object219_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gunter came out for an extended week now that the terrain is getting better.  We’re gonna do the bump jam next wednesday.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;They’ve opened Trestle and some more of the Challenger runs...long haul/short haul, needle’s eye, and boiler.  Cannonball was open on saturday, but not sunday.  Stagecoach is still closed...wind blown!!!  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Got some snow saturday night.  They were forecasting 8-12, but WP only got 5.  Still, better than nothing.  Got out early, and Jane was a madhouse!  Parked at Corona, skied down to Super Gauge, and the singles line was back beyond the ropes!  Did a quick lap through Edelweiss (and cut through the trees to get the pow below pano), but quickly went to Pioneer.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Saw Matthias, Lucille, and Roland over there.  Did *MANY* loops there; Alli, Gunter, and Max joined us.  Alli quickly went off to find Lucille; Max, Gunter, and I went powder hunting.  Good stuff in the Buckaroo trees (but make sure you turn at the road, no matter *what* Gunter says).  Did living room, the weather station, brakeman trees, and wildwood before Max and Gunter bailed.  Met up with Matthias again...took him into lower Topher’s, and did Needle’s Eye.  He bailed back to the base; I did one more run through the brakeman trees.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/22_Weekend_With_Gunter_files/showmap.jpg" length="19817" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Terrain  </title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/14_More_Terrain.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9da02340-cb1f-4528-b5c1-6622300b22b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 06:13:20 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/14_More_Terrain_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object220_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WP got more snow this week...they reported 5” on tuesday and another 4” on wednesday.  I started off with Over’N’Underwood and Engledive...decent.  Still some nasties, but not too bad.  Did Outhouse next...better than Frenchman’s been.  Then went over to the sunnyside, where they had Roundhouse, Bluebell, and the bottom of Edelweiss open.  The bottom section of roundhouse, black section of Columbine, Trestle, and the top of Edelweiss were all closed down.  Not really worth the cruisers...I did Riflesight next.  Decent over there.  Saw the Iron Horse was running, so I *had* to do that.  The top of Arrowhead had a really tough rocky section, but you could ditch around to Spike, and then hit Arrowhead.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The best snow, though, was over on Gambler.  Met Matthias over there...we did a bunch of laps.  Had to finish up on Retta’s and Little Pierre.  Good day...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/14_More_Terrain_files/showmap.jpg" length="22775" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max’s Freestyle Competition</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/8_Maxs_Freestyle_Competition.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0470ac16-465f-46a4-8fd3-db88732e2a32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 8 Jan 2012 07:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/8_Maxs_Freestyle_Competition_files/max.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object221_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:288px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Did get a little snow yesterday...WP reports 6.5”.  They still only have Phantom Bridge, Little 10, and Freeriders open over at the C-lift, and they’re sketchy.  No sunnyside, parsenn, or eagle wind yet either...Retta’s, Outrigger, Over-and-underwood and Engledive are still closed as well...and Pioneer is sketchy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The comp center put on a mini competition today...Max wasn’t so sure to start, but after talking to Dave (and running the course a bunch) yesterday, he decided to sign up.&lt;br/&gt;It was a course on Lower Parkway...some tight alpine turns, then a bump field, then going through a couple teepees to the end.  Speed didn’t matter; you were judged on form.  Max was in the J6’s (8 and under), and he did a great job! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Later that day, we met up with Matthias and played around some.  </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/8_Maxs_Freestyle_Competition_files/max.jpg" length="155262" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year’s Day</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/1_New_Years_Day.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddc51217-98c7-4e7d-bc0f-9c465b456746</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 1 Jan 2012 07:08:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/1_New_Years_Day_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object222_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:147px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Went out early with Max.  We were going to do a Cheshire Cat run, but it looked too hard-packed.  Went over to Jabberwocky instead...evil as well.  At that point, we decided to play around in the park.  </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2012/1/1_New_Years_Day_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="65042" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid X-Mas Report</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/28_Mid_X-Mas_Report.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29101d5d-4044-4dc5-b17d-707d69269682</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 17:06:41 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/28_Mid_X-Mas_Report_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object223_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No snow for a week....but still skiing.  Alli says she’s gonna continue to ski in the dress until it snows. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Took off early today to hit some runs....WP opened Pioneer earlier in the week (even though no new snow...), and reported Spike, Sterling, and Narrow Gauge open.  The bad news...other than Narrow Gauge, all of it was *VERY* sketchy...I don’t think they really should have opened ‘em up.   Here’s a pic from the newly opened Rainbow Cut bottom:&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/28_Mid_X-Mas_Report_files/showmap.jpg" length="21339" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copper Cruisers</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/26_Entry_1.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">274db0fb-429e-4baa-a27d-c246127de018</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 08:09:50 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/26_Entry_1_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object224_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Günter and I did a run to Copper on Monday...figured that if it was cruiser day, we’d go someplace with more stuff open.  They definitely had more terrain than winter park, but still, mostly just cruisers.  The bumps were in about the same troughed-out rocky condition.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It was a little more crowded than earlier in the season, so I wasn’t able to go full throttle on some of the runs, but still, respectable speeds. :)</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/26_Entry_1_files/showmap.jpg" length="23204" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.5” never looked so good</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/22_5.5_never_looked_so_good.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a2c5f1b-dcf6-48d9-9c52-8ea22f95ee33</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 17:39:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/22_5.5_never_looked_so_good_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object225_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Woke up to a little more snow than expected.  The weather report said 1-15degF, so Alli and Max decided to stay home.  I dropped some CH6 on the S7s, and convinced Günter to come out early.  Some places were “dust on crust”, but the HiLo trees were pretty good.  They opened up Cheshire Cat (yay!), and we caught rope drops on Phantom Bridge and Bradley’s Bash.  </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/22_5.5_never_looked_so_good_files/showmap.jpg" length="23839" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Günter Gets Day 1!!!</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/18_Gunter_Gets_Day_1%21%21%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a571a87a-7773-4b3e-a2d7-6276366d5f17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 17:20:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/18_Gunter_Gets_Day_1%21%21%21_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object226_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:213px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Started over at the Zephyr; worked our way over to Jane fairly quickly.  No Cheshire Cat, but Sidetrack and Sleeper were open.  One run down there, and Alli’s calves weren’t happy with her, so Gunter, Max, and I did a couple laps.  After lunch, they opened up Gandy again...MUCH softer and less nasties than it looked from the bottom.  Max was done after a little, so Mom came and got him, and Gunter and I played around some more....hit more bumps, a little trees, and some jumps.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/18_Gunter_Gets_Day_1%21%21%21_files/showmap.jpg" length="20026" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Opens</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/17_Jane_Opens.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba4d517-3cd3-45a2-baa3-c4ca622c4eb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 19:30:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/17_Jane_Opens_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object227_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:216px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Jane opened on Friday...Max and I headed up on Saturday for ATP Devo.  They had Gandy and Frenchman open Friday, but looking up those trails today, I can see why they were closed today!  They did have the bottoms of Spike and Sterling open...but those were evil.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Looks like they’re prepping Cheshire Cat and Sidetrack/Sleeper...hoping that those will open when Gunter is out.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/17_Jane_Opens_files/showmap.jpg" length="23323" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Copper</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/11_More_Copper.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64a1b18a-1812-493f-beac-bce531082390</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 05:56:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/11_More_Copper_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object228_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:223px; height:224px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No real snow for a while at WP...they did open the top of Hughes this weekend, and I see from the website that they have Olympia and whistlestop running as of 12/12, but still no Jane or Hi-Lo.  The weather report says potential for a smaller dump this week, but same “south” pattern, so we’re probably not gonna get much outta it.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Copper’s been doing a good job keeping up with their snowmaking...they’ve got a bunch of stuff open off timberline, as well as the cruisers under super bee.  Did another day trip...having that much terrain open makes it *much* more fun than dodging crowds at WP.  Funny though, the ungroomed stuff off timberline had a lot of nasties sticking out...including the green soliloquy.  That run had a spot with some pretty big bumps...I wouldn’t wanna take a newbie down there.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The blacks off of Excellerator were decent.   Did have to dodge some stuff, but at least you could get some bump work in.  They had Hallelujah open most of the day, and opened up Mine Dump at about 1:30.  I did a couple runs in there before my legs were shot.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/12/11_More_Copper_files/showmap.jpg" length="23768" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Report</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/27_Thanksgiving_Report.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb14bfff-4b27-416e-a627-50e7e8db8aa7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 05:27:53 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Went up to Fraser after the big meal with my parents on thursday.  Looked at the report between WP and copper...copper had more stuff open.  Max decided he didn’t want to ski, and Mom was “iffy”, so they stayed back, whilst I drove down to copper.  Did the pass rather than 9 through Kremmling; takes about 75 min with clear roads and limited traffic.  They opened Windsong under the timberline, so I could bomb that run.  Checked Phresheez, thought the speed must be a mistake, so bombed it again.  Here are the charts:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cranmer Open</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/20_Cranmer_Open.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6f6a13f-efcb-49f3-8be6-6b9aec3783f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 05:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/20_Cranmer_Open_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object229_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:217px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WP opened up Cranmer this weekend.  Got a couple inches, so everything was soft.  Spent the morning playing around with Max and Mom.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/20_Cranmer_Open_files/showmap.jpg" length="19216" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Ski Thin Powder</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/19_How_To_Ski_Thin_Powder.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7225af9a-da22-40d6-92c3-5a55f83f080c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 05:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/19_How_To_Ski_Thin_Powder_files/showmap.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object230_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:218px; height:218px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Headed up solo to Copper; they opened the Flyer lift yesterday.  Coin flip between them and Loveland...Copper’s top-to-bottom doing Excellerator was more appealing.  Good choice...there were some bumps cutting through to Mine Dump, and they opened some of Hallelujah for part of the day.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The vid from below:  cutting from Mine Dump to Trail #20, and hitting some powder.  Alli is pleased to see that this is one of the few times I fell *forward* (rather than back-seating it).  I love the cheering from the lift afterwards...</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/19_How_To_Ski_Thin_Powder_files/showmap.jpg" length="17783" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Park Opening Day   </title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/12_Winter_Park_Opening_Day.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1009ba09-ac9a-42c9-87df-bc91cf33079d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 05:49:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/12_Winter_Park_Opening_Day_files/droppedImage_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object231_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:123px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Winter Park opened 4 days early; Max and I headed up there after hitting Copper the day before.  Not much open...just the Arrow, Gemini, and Endeavor lifts, with Larry Sale, Parkway, and Porcupine open.  Still, got to play around a little with “dueling helmet cams”...I’m playing with the “split image” thing in iMovie. &lt;br/&gt; </description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/12_Winter_Park_Opening_Day_files/droppedImage_1.jpg" length="59207" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copper:  Day 1 for Glenn and Max</title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/11_Copper__Day_1_for_Glenn_and_Max.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80259a02-a66b-4ae5-9963-a2b3ac8d708d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 21:22:50 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/11_Copper__Day_1_for_Glenn_and_Max_files/droppedImage_3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object232_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:214px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Mom’s out of town, Max has veteran’s day off, so we decide to hit Copper.  Max had never been there before, so he dug it...even though there were really only two trails open.  Main Vein under the American Eagle was okay...at least it has a little pitch to it.  Excelerator was also open, serving race-only Copperopolis, and Ptarmigan, which eventually grew some mini-bumps.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/11/11_Copper__Day_1_for_Glenn_and_Max_files/droppedImage_3.jpg" length="83526" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alli Gets Day #1 </title>
      <link>http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/10/18_Alli.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c79f59d4-0029-475a-aefd-c77ebf5bd4d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 05:41:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/10/18_Alli_files/droppedImage.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Media/object233_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:216px; height:290px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Wolf Creek opened the weekend of the 8th...they got 3’ of freshies.  A-Basin opened last thursday, beating out Loveland, who opened last friday.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Alli once again wins the “first turns” award this year...while they only had the “icy ribbon of death” open, she still was skiing while we all were working.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://matrix-pi1.local/mountain_house/Mountain_House/2011_2012/Entries/2011/10/18_Alli_files/droppedImage.jpg" length="84092" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
